[{"answer": "Well, I think it has an impact both on what's going to happen in the fall and more important what happens after that.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "But what does this really mean in the context of the national election, do you think?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, I think the benefit of what happened on Tuesday was the power of ideas.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, again, I would probably eagerly persuade him that the best person in Wisconsin to put on the ticket is indeed Paul Ryan.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "But if Romney called you and said, right, I've thought about this, you are my man, I presume you wouldn't turn him down?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "ALKER: I think he'd have a pretty tough person to convince in terms of my wife, Tonette, after all this campaigning, all this focus in Wisconsin.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "He decides not Paul Ryan, it's going to be Scott Walker?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, I think it -- you know, it's interesting.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What do you make about this furor over President Clinton's comments, which have been, it appears, completely at odds with President Obama's positions in relation to Mitt Romney in particular and to the Bush tax cuts?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Is that accurate?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I know his critics, not only Republican critics but even some of his Democratic critics see something a little bit more sinister.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Is it really likely that he would have said these things which are so on the face of it, diametrically opposed to President Obama's main key election battle grounds as a mistake or could it be something a little bit more sinister?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Very emotional for me.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What was it like to see your son elected president?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I think he felt badly for his son, and -- when his son was criticized.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "You, as his friend, what do you think?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Chaz, how are you?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Well, I was just trying to think back to our last encounter, and what an extraordinary twist to your life that's gone on ever since.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "How are you doing?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I mean, I think it put some pressure on the relationship.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "How much pressure did the fact that you decided to become a man -- how much pressure did that put on the relationship, do you think, looking back?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "You know, I think that she did.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Did you feel that she ever fully embraced what you were doing?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "I mean, it wasn't a pleasant thing to do, you know, honestly.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Do you regret doing that, with hindsight?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Yeah I mean, I think we both cared very deeply for each other.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Have you managed to stay friends?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not the most outgoing fellow.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "How are you finding that?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "You know, I think that it just -- when that first started with those type of people, I just kind of let it roll off my back.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "What did you feel when all that bile was being spilled in your direction?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "You know, we really -- we really don't.", "docId": "120607pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do you and your stepmother have lively debates about this, Chaz?", "qSentId": 526}]